Ever since I got bitten by that spider,
I only had one week
where my life has felt normal.
That was when you found out.
When you botched that spell
where you wanted everyone
to forget that Peter Parker is Spider-Man,
We started getting some visitors.
From every universe.
Hello, Peter.
You're not Peter Parker.
Sorry, what was your name again?
Dr. Otto Octavius.
Wait no, seriously,
what's your actual name?
There are others out there.
We need to send them back.
So,
Scooby-Doo this crap!
You know, all this is
kinda your mess.
I know a couple of magic words myself
starting with the word "please".
Please,
Scooby-Doo this crap.
You're flying out into the darkness,
to fight ghosts.
What do you mean?
They all die fighting Spider-Man.
It's their fate.
I'm sorry, kid.
Yeah, me too.
Don't-
Look, there has to be another way!
There isn't.
They're a danger to our universe.
You'll never take this away from me.
Peter...
You're struggling
to have everything you want
while the world tries to make you choose.
This is all my fault.
I can't save everyone.
What's happening?
They're starting to come through.
And I can't stop them.