Hey, you!
Pay attention to the customers!
Your job is to fuck the clients.
He's disgusting.
Who do you think you are?
Queen Meeru?
I'm not going to hurt you.
You're far from home and so am I.
You and I...
...we are alike.
We've been hurt...
...betrayed...our trust has been broken.
We both know fear.
Yet, the biggest fear we both face...
...is the fear of ourselves.
Let's show them we're not afraid.
Let's show them we're more
than the shackles that bind us.
Your patience is appreciated
and I can assure you...
...Devra is aware of your presence.
A decision
when to receive you is imminent.
Thank you, Levitica, honored King.
We await their arrival.
Darian, Devra, greetings.
I beg you...