ONE YEAR LATER...
THE TSJ VIRUS SPREADS:
EUROPE CLOSES BORDERS WITH RUSSIA
WELCOME TO THE BEGINNING
OF THE END
FOR SALE
FORGIVE US LORD
BARCELONA
BOARDING
CANCELLED
GRAN CANARIA
Civil Security Alert
TEMPORARY STATE OF ALERT
6,4 KM TO PONTEVEDRA
STATE OF EMERGENCY
A State of Emergency is declared
in all national territory
due to special circumstances
in order to preserve order and integrity.
Measures and restrictions
will be implemented:
FROM 2:00PM ALL COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY
IS SUSPENDED.
THE POPULATION MAY BE MILITARIZED
Comply with authority
for your safety.
EVACUATION
VEHICLE
Don't get on that bus
Please, stay in the house
We'll come find you
soon
TWO WEEKS LATER...
NOTICE OF MANDATORY EVACUATION
ALL RESIDENTS OF THIS ZONE
AND OUTLYING AREAS
MUST BE EVACUATED
BEGINNING 14:00H 10/04/25
ENERGY STORAGE SYSTEM
LITHIUM BATTERY
IT WON'T DEFEAT US
THANK YOU FOR THESE DAYS
NOW YOU HAVE TO SAVE YOURSELF
SAN LOURENZO HOSPITAL
Notifications
Belén
BELÉN - ANSWER
APOCALYPSE Z:
THE BEGINNING OF THE END