Although inspired by the life
of Bruno Sulak,
this film is fiction.
Characters, situations, places
and certain events
might be modified or reinvented
to express the author's artistic vision.
Ladies and gentlemen, nobody move.
This is a robbery.
No one will get hurt if you do as I say.
Tie your hands.
- I have two kids.
- You can tell that to the cops.
The tape.
Open the cash drawers slowly.
Fill up the bag.
Fill up the bag that has been provided.
The checkout at the far end, get the bills
together and give them to number 2.
Morning, ma'am. I'm gonna take a lollipop.
Here. Tie your hands, sit down.
And remember, this money is not yours.
- Hurry up. Do as he says.
- Thank you, Nicole.
Relax, it's not your money.
- Checks as well?
- Yes, checks and bills, thank you.
Good. There.
It's easy, right? Thank you.
Have a lovely day.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Can you hold this? It's too sweet.
Have a pleasant day.
Apologies for the inconvenience.
And I'll see you soon.
Hey!
Careful. Watch the road, Annie.
- So this isn't your bag?
- No.
And what's in it is not yours either?
No, it's not.
What are you doing here, then?
- I don't know.
- Well, you're innocent.
Damn. That was very nearly
a miscarriage of justice.
I was this close to sending him to prison.
Excuse me. Sorry.
I'm sorry. You can go.
I'm sorry.
Wait, Tonio, tell me one thing.
How many times have I arrested you?
- Give me a number.
- I don't know.
Six... Maybe seven times.
Seventeen times.
Sit down.
Come on, the old lady recognized you.
Boss, there's been a robbery
at the Orange Continent.
- The Orange Continent?
- The old Unico.
- Shit. Any casualties?
- None.
Well, that's something.
How much?
Around 200k. This week's takings.
We've identified one of the guys
from a photo.
Sulak Bruno, born on November 6th, '55,
in Sidi Bel Abbès, Algeria.
Legionnaire in the 2nd REP,
deserted 18 months ago.
Does he have a record?
He did four months for theft
when he was 18.
Small stuff.
Since he deserted,
he's upgraded his business,
he's suspected in a dozen robberies.
Always supermarkets.
Avignon, Albi, Beaune.
Always the same crew. Two of them,
plus one who waits in the car.
- Who identified him?
- Two employees.
They were in the robbery.
- They're here.
- Could they be accomplices?
Honestly, everything's possible,
but I doubt it.
- Bring them in. I'll talk to them.
- Okay.
- No, leave the photo here.
Tonio, my boy.
This is your lucky day.
Get out of here, I'm tired of you.
Just go before I change my mind.
The black and white doesn't help.
You can't see the color of his eyes.
- It's a bit stiff.
- But mugshots, you know...
No one looks great in profile.
He's better looking in person.
Eyes like that are really unforgettable.
And his smile. A big smile.
- Lovely.
- A handsome boy.
And polite.
Good-looking.
Really good-looking.
Wait, ladies,
we're talking about a robber.
Not some pretty boy in a club.
Your little angel has stolen 20 million.
Yes, well, I...
- And the other?
- The other?
- What other?
- The other guy.
I couldn't really see.
- I didn't pay attention, sorry.
- Me neither.
Thank you, ladies.
Who is this clown?
- One.
- What?
Forget it.
I don't believe you, you won't do it.
- Two.
- Stop it.
It's stupid,
we don't even know how deep it is.
Bruno.
- I'm serious. Very serious.
- You're very serious?
If you do this, I won't talk to you
for the rest of the day.
- The rest of the day? That's a long time.
- Very long.
- Three.
- Bruno, stop.
I'm serious. I'm scared.
I love you too.
No!
Yeah, right.
Very funny.
Come up now.
Bruno!
You're a dick!
Fuck!
You're a dick.
I... You scared me.
You're as crazy as I am.
You didn't know that?
Do you know what I love the most?
Besides me?
Besides you.
The wind on the skin.
The wind that caresses.
And you?
- Besides you?
- Yes.
The speed.
Do you know what I wanted to do
when I was young?
- No.
- A lot of things.
- What's stopping you?
- Nothing.
I'll do them all one day.
- Do you know what I like the most?
- No.
When the sky and the sea meet
and you can't see the horizon.
We'll go live by the sea.
And we'll have a baby.
What?
- Hi. I'm Bruno.
- Annie, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
We can share a bottle.
Sounds good. Who's that?
Marika's here.
Look at my princess.
- I thought you were coming tonight.
- Hi!
Nope.
- How are you?
- My princess.
Come have a drink.
This is beautiful.
I'm happy to see you.
- What do you think of the view?
- It's not too bad.
Over there is Le Château de ma mère.
And over there, La Gloire de mon père.
And he just jumped on him.
On his shoulders.
And he just bit his neck.
Seriously. His tendons were...
- That's not what happened.
- Yes, it is.
You can't say that, Bruno.
It's a matter of common sense.
You have no common sense.
You can't say that politics is useless.
Politics only helps the rich to stay rich,
and the poor have to shut up.
You're exhausting,
you don't believe in anything.
I believe in freedom.
And Chirac, Marchais
and Mitterrand won't give it to us.
I disagree.
- Who's taking the second share?
- You.
But my share is your share.
Everybody did the job,
everybody gets paid.
I don't care, I don't want it.
Give me the checks.
Can you believe it?
We've given a lot of groceries
to a lot of good people.
But we should tell these good people,
because instead of thanking you,
they want to see you in jail.
- Robin Hood.
- We haven't done anything wrong.
Except stealing from
bigger thieves than us.
Don't worry,
the big cats never go to jail.
- Communist!
- It's not about that,
I just want to blow everything up.
Terrorist, then.
- Are you messing with me?
- No.
What?
Nothing.
You're handsome.
Ladies and gentlemen, nobody move.
This is a robbery.
Do as I say and everything will be fine.
Hurry up!
SUPERMARKET COOP
Nobody move, this is a robbery!
Do as I say, and no one will get hurt.
Open the cash drawers.
Empty them in this bag. Hello, ma'am.
The 500 bills together,
the 100 bills together.
- Come on, baby.
- You have to put it behind.
Look.
- Amazing.
- You got me closer.
- That's our ball.
- That's two points.
Should we start again?
- Hola, cabrones!
- Patrick.
Behind the mountain.
You're not ready to play now.
- I'm exhausted.
- It's nice to see you.
What do we have to drink?
Some friends of mine had a vineyard,
amazing wines.
They could mess with your head.
But apparently,
it was back in the 12th, 13th century.
- Wines that drive you mad?
- Or blind.
That's totally bullshit.
- It doesn't happen with all the grapes.
- You said that.
- Okay, I'm going back up.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Are you coming with me?
- Are you coming?
- I'll be right there.
- Be careful.
- Don't worry, I worked in a restaurant.
Put the knife down.
- You're trying to calm me down.
- Calm down.
You're trying to calm me down, I know you.
I know you.
This feels nice.
Patrick, listen to me if you want to come.
Why not that one? It's closer.
No. We've already hit
all the supermarkets in the area.
No, we haven't done that one,
outside Rodez.
Which one is it? Continent, Mammouth?
My dear Continent lover, it's a Mammouth.
Patrick, you go in after me,
you hold the cashiers at bay.
- And where am I, Bruno?
- You, my love,
you're in the parking lot,
ready, engine going.
Okay. What kind of car do we have?
- A Renault 30.
- No, I said I wanted a BMW.
- It's fine.
- They're heavy, not reliable.
We tried to get another one.
I want a BMW, guys.
It's about the driver, not the car.
- Is everybody ready?
- Ready.
- No worries.
- We'll go at six o'clock tomorrow morning.
- Don't party too hard.
- You too, Pat.
I'll check the plan one more time.
Okay, let's go. Good night, everyone.
Just in case...
Give the bag to the next cashier.
Come on, it'll be over soon.
Fill it.
Next register, thank you.
Please stay calm.
- What are you doing?
- Fill up the bag.
- You coon, you're not Al Capone.
- I'll show you.
- What's up?
- Patrick, cable ties, go on.
- What do I do?
- Cable ties!
Everybody stay calm.
Nobody moves, hands on the counter.
I don't want to die, I have a little girl.
Shut up. On the counter.
- Load it. Shut up.
- You'll pay for this.
- Load it.
- Drago?
Fill up the bag!
Hands on the counter!
Listen to me, fuck!
I said shut up!
- What's wrong? You got this?
- We're fine.
- Tell me.
You're not going to die, calm down.
Nothing will happen. Relax!
Get your hands off me. Relax.
Shut up, stop moving!
Stop moving!
- Are you insane?
- Move.
- Listen to me! Calm down.
- I don't want to die.
- What is he doing?
- Move.
Breathe, relax.
- I can't breathe.
- Stop.
I can't brea...
Look at me.
- Relax, Brigitte.
- Breathe.
- I can't! Help, I can't do it!
- Look at me, stay with me.
Let's bounce.
- What's going on?
- Shush.
What shush? Calm down, boy.
What? What's going on?
- Why did you do that?
- Did you kill someone?
Next time, I'll kill you.
- Is that a threat?
- Yes.
We're here for the money,
not to kill people.
- Are you threatening me?
- Yes.
I didn't kill anyone,
this thing just went off!
- Calm down.
- Shut up!
We're fine, nothing happened, calm down.
Don't do that ever again!
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
- What's the story?
- He recognized Sulak from the photo.
Take everything. The other side, too.
Hello. Tell me what happened.
She's the cashier who got attacked.
I'll go talk to her.
They came in, we got violently attacked.
They pointed their guns at us,
they were shouting.
- How many were they?
- Four or five.
- Can you describe them?
- Yes.
One big Black guy.
A beast with bloody eyes.
And a small hysterical white guy.
In my opinion... You know?
He was screaming, shouting, shooting.
And a blond guy with blue eyes,
in a complete panic too.
He was rude to everyone. Very rude.
- And then?
- I screamed, and they all left.
- And they took nothing?
- They took our takings.
I can humbly say that I saved lives.
That's great.
So? What do you think?
With dumbasses like him,
we will never catch Sulak.
For sure.
We're organizing having drinks tonight,
for your departure.
A farewell party? I don't like that.
Warm bubbly, cold appetizers.
Drunk officers trying
to hook up with the receptionist.
- Pathetic.
- It makes the guys happy.
It's not every day you get promoted
to Chief of Organized Crime.
We need to celebrate.
If you say so.
Ciao.
- What?
- Let's get out of here.
- Now?
- Pack your things.
Get dressed, pack a bag,
meet me downstairs.
Don't turn on the light.
Drago, Marika, let's get out of here.
Take the BMW, we'll see you in Paris.
Patrick! Wake up. We're leaving!
- What's happening?
- He thinks the cops are coming.
- Drago, move!
- Coming.
Shit.
It's crazy how you can feel
they're coming. How do you do that?
- Fuck!
- Did you see that?
- Are we going to Paris?
- Let's go, mi amor.
I told Drago. It's over, I'm out.
I've had enough of the police raids.
No more prison, no more lawyers,
no more packages. Enough.
I've had enough.
He promised he would stop.
- Drago never went to prison?
- No.
But it always ends up with prison.
Who ended up in jail?
My ex.
He died in there.
A settling of scores.
What are you thinking? Banks?
Banks are all connected
to local police stations.
Armed security, traceable bills.
Foreign exchange counters?
No. You know what's good?
Fancy jewelers.
Jewelry is nice, it's small, fancy.
I'm a thug's girl, that's it,
That's how it is, I can't change.
And you?
I'm not a thug's girl, I'm with an artist.
A poet, an outsider, a rebel.
Everything he does, he does well.
He tried rollerblading,
he was a natural. Jumps, tricks...
- Backflips.
- You're addicted.
We are addicted, yeah.
Drago drives me crazy too.
But I won't put mine on rollerblades.
What are we doing with a loser like him?
He's nothing but trouble.
You know, if it wasn't for the fact
he's your friend...
Yes, but he's my friend.
- Okay, but be careful.
- I'll talk to him.
- You know what?
- What?
If they go to jail...
- Let's end up together.
- Sure.
Deal!
I don't understand, why aren't we dancing?
- We're going.
- Let's go.
Let's go!
Hey. Tell me, Bruno.
Your bling, who will you flog it to?
- My bling?
- Yeah.
We'll flog it back to them,
or the insurance companies.
That's a good plan.
That's smart, it could work.
What's this idiot doing now?
He's messing with a guy
he shouldn't mess with.
- Do you know him?
- Yeah,
Steve. He's from Yugoslavia.
Go talk to him, he's gonna crush him.
- I want him to get crushed.
- Go.
Steve...
It's paradise here.
French cops are babies.
French prisons are better
than hotels in Yugoslavia.
It's paradise, I'm telling you.
- Are you working?
- Here and there.
I was Belmondo's bodyguard.
Belmondo? Seriously?
I even shot a movie with him.
Hear that? He knows Belmondo.
Belmondo, damn. That's awesome.
I'm sleeping where Belmondo...
Not sure you'd be into it,
but if you want to work with me,
I may have something in the works.
We'll see.
Hello, sir. Welcome.
What can I do for you?
I'd like to see your earrings.
Of course, follow me.
Is it for a special occasion?
- An anniversary?
- Wedding anniversary.
- Very well. Do you have a budget in mind?
- No, I thought...
Ladies and gentlemen, this is a robbery.
Everything will be fine.
I'll handle it. Your hands, please.
On the floor, sir. On the floor.
Your hands, please. Hands.
Go. Fifty seconds.
Stay calm. We're here for the jewelry.
Nobody will get hurt.
Stay calm, thank you.
No noise. It'll soon be over.
Thirty seconds.
Let's go!
Thank you for cooperating.
Have a lovely day.
It was a pleasure doing business with you.
- And have a nice weekend.
- Thanks.
Great job!
Let's go.
- Shit, there are two cars behind us.
- Relax.
- What are you doing?
- I'll handle it.
Move!
They think they own the place.
It's always the same.
Calm down, I'll take care of it.
- I'm calm, I just need to pick up my kids.
- Excuse me.
Move. You're blocking traffic, sir.
Stay calm.
- You can go, ma'am, move.
- Thank you, officer.
- I'm telling you, this bastard...
- Can I get a coffee?
- He attacked me.
- Shut up!
One at a time!
Want me to sit down?
Sit down!
I'll press charges.
What the hell?
We can hear you from over there.
I'm the victim,
but these assholes won't listen.
What did you say?
Assholes... What's going on?
He says his client didn't pay him.
They had a fight. Nothing new.
We found this on him.
Drugs, soliciting, assault, theft.
That's quite the list.
Get me out of here
and I'll give you a crew.
A crew? Who? What crew?
Yugoslavs. They're planning a robbery.
I know one of them.
But... Keep going, I'm interested.
Take these off me, then we'll talk.
- And my complaint?
- We'll write it down.
Take it. Come with me.
- And I want my money.
- Don't push it.
The Jaeger-LeCoultre I told you about.
A platinum model
with automatic perpetual movement.
Classic and modern.
It's very popular.
Do you like it?
- Is that a yes or a no?
- Yes, I said.
Could we...
- Can I put it on you?
- Of course.
- Isn't it a bit heavy?
- No, I don't think so.
- How much is it?
- This model is 63,000 francs.
I see. I better not lose it then.
Or have it stolen, because these days...
There are so many robberies, you know?
Listen...
I'll take it.
- Very good. Will you keep it on?
- Yes, please.
I'll let you talk to my colleague
about the payment.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Congratulations, it's a fine piece.
Thank you. Can I get a discount?
I don't think that's possible.
What if I pay cash?
In that case, I can give you 3% off.
Five.
Three point five.
Three point five...
I'll take it.
It's nice.
- What time is it?
- 7:00.
You always get up early.
Let me sleep.
- Croissants?
- Yes.
- My love?
- Yes, my love?
Can you get me tampons?
Of course, my love.
Thank you.
You don't know any of these guys, right?
- That's right.
- Sure.
- And you? Miss...
- Braumann, Sophie. No.
No, what?
No, I don't know them.
Sophie Braumann.
That's Alsatian, Braumann.
- My parents are from Bordeaux.
- Bordeaux?
That's a beautiful city.
The Saint-Jean neighborhood,
the Saint-André cathedral,
the Garonne, the canelé cakes.
- The wine, sometimes.
- Why the hell am I here?
What do you think?
I don't know this girl,
we hooked up last night.
If I had known...
It's dangerous to follow strangers.
Has your mother from Bordeaux
never told you that?
No, sir. She never told me that.
Okay.
Stop taking me for a fool, both of you.
Your little act is worn out.
You, honey,
I'll arrest you as an accessory.
Criminal conspiracy.
Fake ID, because they are fake IDs, right?
And possession of stolen goods,
or do you have a receipt for the necklace?
Accessory to what? Are you insane?
Leave her alone.
Do you know the women's wing
at La Santé prison?
It's no Club Med.
Especially for a pretty chick like you.
She's gonna make a lot of friends. A lot.
I didn't do anything,
I don't know this guy, we fucked once.
I hope he was good,
because you're gonna pay for it.
You're looking at five years in jail,
at least.
When you're out, you'll be broken.
Screwed.
You won't be able to work again,
I'll make sure of that.
You'll have to work the streets
to pay for your fix.
One morning,
you'll end up dead in a dumpster
behind a bar with a syringe in your arm.
I don't do drugs.
- Not yet, but it will happen.
- I didn't do anything.
- The court will decide.
- Enough!
Stop.
- Why do you care?
- Fine, you win.
Leave her alone, I'll talk.
There you go.
What do I get in return?
I'll give you all the robberies
if you leave her alone.
And your buddies?
What buddies?
- Pérez?
- Yes, boss?
- Come pick up the lady.
- Okay, boss. I'm on my way.
- Okay, come on.
- It's okay.
- Ouch.
- Come on.
Let's go!
- What you did is really shitty.
- I know.
I'm listening.
Finally, the Cora supermarket in Beaune,
was that you?
Yes.
Tell me more.
You won't arrest her, right?
I gave you my word.
- Yeah.
- I did.
I'll talk to the judge,
she'll get probation.
What about her fake IDs?
What do you want to know?
I went in, I robbed the place and I left.
End of story.
- Alone?
- Yes.
You say you robbed 19 supermarkets
in eight months. Impressive.
Always alone?
- Always alone.
- No, I don't buy that.
I'll tell you what I think.
You were with your buddy Drago,
and the girl was waiting in the car.
I don't know any Dragan.
Dragan? We busted your buddies.
Stop playing stupid, Bruno.
Come on, you have enough
to make the judge hard.
No, I'm very greedy,
that's my biggest flaw.
Well, it's mine too.
By the way, I need a favor.
What is it?
Can I keep my watch?
Your watch? What's so special
about your Kelton?
It's my dad's.
He gave it to me, it's precious to me.
The guards will take it from me
if I have it when I go in.
If it's a sentimental piece...
Thank you.
Let me say goodbye, please.
Be quick.
My love.
I love you.
- Come with me.
- I'll wait for you.
I love you.
Let's go, lovebirds.
Hi.
What are you in for?
- Miscarriage of justice. You?
- Same.
I got 12 years for armed robbery.
You?
Awaiting trial.
I don't like the decor in here.
And the food looks disgusting.
I don't plan on staying.
Jean-Loup Lablache.
Bruno Sulak.
I know.
I don't think guards make enough money.
I could have something for you.
I could be interested.
But not here. Move.
You know where to find me.
My love, every day, with my words,
I caress your skin with the tip of my pen.
And your lips too.
You know,
they want to make a beast out of me,
but no matter how much they try
with force or ruse,
I won't give in.
I want to live the life I want,
to stay the boy that is exhilarated,
like in the Reggiani song
that you like so much.
To stay the person who is amazed,
who dreams, who is waiting for you.
Life, my love, is not eternal.
I'm alive, alive when I write to you,
when I smell sometimes
the wind brushing my skin.
- How do we do it?
- Seventy-one.
Okay.
Hands on the table, old hand.
That's nice. I like it.
That's good stuff.
We can make a trident with this.
Tie them together, it'll hold.
It's strong.
- Will you get more?
- Of course I will.
You were right,
I like being an outsider,
different, like an artist.
In another life,
I could have been a painter or a writer.
But here, in prison,
there's no room for culture.
We are misunderstood, abandoned.
They won't get to me, I don't want
to fall into hatred and violence.
I'm stronger than this
and I'll be back more alive than ever.
I got 12 years in the slammer,
I've done nearly six now.
When I get out, I think...
I'll do simple things.
Chowing down by the sea.
Maybe in the mountains?
I'm not saying
that I'll shack up with a goat.
All clear.
Wait. It's holding. No, wait.
Come on.
Let me... Shit.
Yes! That's it.
Let's go!
- Come on.
- Slowly.
Jump!
Come on, Jean-Loup!
Come on!
Come on, you're almost there.
Give me your hand.
Come on, Jean-Loup.
You're almost there, Jean-Loup,
take my hand. Come on.
Good, hurry up.
- Come on, Jean-Loup!
- I won't make it.
- Come on!
- I won't make it, Bruno.
Jean-Loup! Jean-Loup!
Come on, damn it!
Get out of here, Bruno.
Get out of here, brother.
- Jean-Loup.
- Get out of here. I won't make it.
I'll come back for you.
Let's go!
Hello?
What do you mean, "he escaped?"
Okay.
No, no, no.
BRUNO SULAK DRAPED IN JEWELS
POLICE ON SULAK'S HEELS
SULAK, THE STAR
- He's making fools out of us.
- Why are you obsessed with him?
He's not
one of those trigger-happy idiots.
Cartier in Geneva, hit twice in two weeks.
Why does he do it? For the thrill!
He doesn't give a shit about the money.
How much did he make with the robberies?
One hundred, 150?
He doesn't give a shit,
he just enjoys doing it.
We need to figure out why he does it,
then we'll be able to nail him.
- Move your asses.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, guys.
Let's move.
- Shake down your snitches, but find him.
- Okay.
Anyone got a cigarette?
Do you mind?
A lighter?
Flat whites are not good for digestion.
What do you want?
Nothing. We thought we'd have
breakfast with you.
That's nice.
Were you in the neighborhood?
You know,
every cop in the country is after you.
We'll bust you,
in a week, a month, a year.
We'll see about that, pal.
Why did you come here?
To tell you to back off.
Don't you have other guys to catch?
You're my favorite.
You're mine too.
Mine too.
Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
- Anytime.
- This is a bit mad, right?
- A bit.
Let's go. Come on.
- Hello.
- Delostane.
- Go ahead.
Thank you.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Come in, step to the side.
Raise your arms.
Don't move.
On the ground.
- Open the door. Now.
- Open it.
- Open it!
- Don't move.
Go over to your friend,
lie down on the floor next to him.
There. On the floor.
Hello, gentlemen.
First, let my friend in.
- Done.
- Done?
Good job.
Cuff yourselves to the heater.
I want the key to the cell.
Jean-Loup Lablache's.
- Now.
- Thank you.
Michel, how was your daughter's recital?
Very good, thank you.
- Number 12.
Sit down.
Cuff yourselves.
Gate!
Gate. Open the gate.
Good.
Gate.
- What do you smoke?
- Gauloises.
- Not very strong.
- Unfiltered.
I thought it was stronger.
You're crazy.
- You're amazing.
- I told you I'd be back.
My friends are back.
- Bye, guys.
- Goodbye, gentlemen.
- It was a pleasure.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Have a nice day.
- See you.
Bastards.
Fuck!
Those guys have some balls.
Goodbye.
You guys are insane.
ID, cash, you've got everything.
And a ticket to Rio, through Lisbon.
Your name is Carlos.
Stop it, guys, I'm gonna cry!
- We'll be there soon.
- Thank you.
- Room 14, second floor.
The door!
I love you.
- What are you watching?
- A sad movie.
Hello? Can I speak to Franchet?
It's a private matter.
- Is it good?
- It's sad. I like it.
Franchet, it's me.
I've got the rocks. Yes.
Twenty-five million.
In new francs, it's at least 100k.
Yes.
Tomorrow, midday. Pompidou Centre.
Okay, let's do that.
Come into my arms, my love.
It's too sad.
We got a lead. You'll like this.
Only one man. Where is the location
for the exchange?
- Franchet, the insurer.
- Yeah, at Beaubourg.
- Beaubourg.
- Pompidou Centre?
- When?
- Twelve o'clock.
- Twelve.
- Yeah.
- Circular motion, I said.
- Yes.
Quiet, please.
The court is now in session.
Will the defendant rise, please.
Your name is Sulak Bruno, born
November 6th, 1955, in Sidi Bel Abbès.
Yugoslavian nationality.
I'm not Yugoslavian,
I'm French, Your Honor.
My father is French from Poland,
like Michel Poniatowski,
and my mother is a pied-noir,
like Marthe Villalonga.
Quiet, please. Good.
You are being charged for
fraudulently taking away cash
to the detriment of supermarkets,
Mammouth, Atac and Rallye,
between July 6th and 20th, 1983.
These acts were committed
as a part of a group,
and with use of a weapon
or threat thereof.
As well as criminal conspiracy.
Before we hear the testimony
of the lead investigator,
do you have anything to say?
I do, Your Honor.
You may speak.
You know,
I was an excellent soldier. Excellent.
And I became an excellent outcast,
just as I could I have become
an excellent cop or magistrate.
I surely doubt it.
What I would like for you to understand,
ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
and to you too,
Mr. Self-Righteous Prosecutor,
is that I don't recognize your court
or your justice.
You mean nothing to me,
I deny you the right to judge me.
The court takes note of this.
And neither Annie, Patrick nor Drago
were ever my accomplices.
That is not what the investigation
brought proof of.
Just like in astrology,
the police can say whatever they want.
Enough.
Sulak, we won't tolerate your impudence.
Impudence is all I have left.
Fine, sit down.
Defendant Drago, please rise.
He's not a proper Yugoslavian either.
Will the defendants please rise?
After due consideration,
the court and the jury
sentence each of you
to three years in prison.
As for yourself, madam,
since there were no previous convictions,
you are sentenced to 18 months in prison,
which will be suspended
and served on probation.
You will be subjected to strict controls
for a period of two years.
I'd like to say one more thing.
Mr. Sulak, before you continue
your tour of France's court system
for your many other offenses,
please know that
if you don't change your attitude,
the sentences will be extremely serious.
Court is adjourned.
Pick a card.
Do you really think
that you'd have been a good cop?
Of course I do.
Finally, the card
I was waiting two rounds for.
Why did you desert the legion?
Long story.
To validate my freefall world record,
I had to sign up for another five years.
Five years.
Why didn't you do it?
You seemed happy.
You don't understand.
No one tells me what to do.
No one. Ever.
Pick a card.
No one tells me what to do either.
No one. Ever.
That's stupid, we could have been pals.
I could have shown you the ropes.
- The ropes?
- Of life.
- Life?
- Yes, your life is too restricted,
you're caught
between your bosses and felons.
I am free.
Really, you're free?
You're really free.
Do you think
you're the only adventurer here?
We live the adventure too,
on the other side.
You, you're either on the run
or in the clink.
What kind of freedom is that?
But you see, I chose this life.
Even in jail, I'm freer than you.
Sure. Here we go, three sixes.
- Shit.
- Discard.
You're a lucky bastard, seriously.
Why did you go back for Jean-Loup?
I promised him. And I'm a nice guy.
You are a nice guy.
- Of course.
- We both know that.
The nicer you are,
the more people like you.
The more they like you,
the more famous you get.
And the more popular you get.
The more you annoy people.
Pick a card.
Excuse me.
The gun.
In my bag.
Follow me.
Get in and shut up.
Close the door. I'm watching you.
So you want to play, right?
Take that! Rummy.
Didn't see that coming, right?
Moréas, are you sleepy?
You're a humble guy.
You want to play.
I don't want to play, I want to win.
Hello. Don't move, guys.
- Let's go.
- No, thanks.
I'd love that.
Guns in the bag, and the handcuff key.
Now.
- Let me keep mine, it means a lot.
- In that case...
Are you sure?
I'm too old to be on the run.
Good luck.
- Bye.
Have a nice day.
Can you drop me off?
Spectacular escape
in the Corail train from Montpellier
to Lyon this afternoon.
A commando group made up
of several armed individuals
managed to free the now
infamous Bruno Sulak,
as well as one of his accomplices,
while they were being transferred
to the Lyon penitentiary.
The fugitives are still at large,
despite the large contingent
of police officers on their trail.
Thank you for today.
Moving on, the economy.
EEC finance ministers are meeting
in Brussels
to raise by one point
the interest rate of central banks,
which means that it will be
more difficult for households
to get loans.
And they call us thieves.
We need to go. Far away.
Let's go someplace warm, please.
In the sun.
To Los Angeles!
Chaplin's country.
- Jim Morrison's country.
- Los Angeles.
Land of jewels.
Novica Zivkovic.
That's my real name.
- Hello?
- Yes, pal. It's me, it's Bruno.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry about the other day,
we didn't have time for the rematch.
But we'll meet again very soon.
Sooner than you think.
I'm not so sure.
Where are you? Are you in Paris?
We could have a drink one of these days.
Of course, you'll come alone.
- Of course.
- Sure, why not? I'll think about it.
I have to go.
I can't say "See you soon," pal.
He's here, he's in Paris,
you need to find him!
- Hello.
- I'm here to report.
- Sure.
POLICE STATION
- Hello.
- I'm here to report.
- Thank you.
Annie Bragnier.
- It's been two days. Move!
- Leave me alone.
- No.
- Come on.
It'll put a smile on your face
Come on, Annie
I'll make you a wonderful meal.
Oh, yes, my little Annie
- Hello.
- Annie Bragnier, reporting.
- What's up?
- It's been so long!
Are you ready?
- Ready? We're going on vacation.
- Really?
My love, what are you drinking?
- How about some ice cream?
- Sure.
- Pistachio.
I'll get you one.
- Want some ice cream?
- No, I'm good.
Steve?
Are we on vacation?
What are you doing?
I'm leaving, I've had enough. Move.
Why?
I thought we were on vacation.
We can be on vacation and work.
I don't think it's funny.
It's gonna end badly, you know?
What are you afraid of?
Nothing. I just don't want it
to end badly.
Actually, I am afraid for you and Steve.
See, you're afraid.
Do you want me to quit?
I never asked you to quit.
But I'll never ask you to keep doing it.
So what do you want, then?
I just want a few days of peace with you.
You were gone to America for months.
Just the two of us, for two days,
just two minutes, okay?
- Stop.
- When are you gonna stop?
Don't you see? I won't be there.
I won't be there when you get arrested.
Honestly, the Cartier in Cannes,
you must both be insane.
We won't get arrested. Annie, come on.
Okay?
We won't get arrested.
Annie!
Forty million francs worth of jewels.
That's the loot of the robbers
who attacked Cartier in Cannes yesterday.
The two robbers were identified
by the police.
The man is a Yugoslavian,
Bruno Sulak, "The Legionnaire",
he already took part in
- in most of the robberies.
- Annie! Bruno is on TV!
Around 12.30 p.m.,
two people came in together.
About one minute apart.
And they asked to see some pieces.
Thanks to one of the employees' testimony,
the robbers were easily identified.
They're two Yugoslavians,
Bruno Sulak and Radisa Jovanovic.
Bruno Sulak, "The Legionnaire",
is well-known to the police.
Bruno Sulak.
Bruno Sulak, the offender...
The uncatchable thief...
The man who escaped twice...
The modern-day Arsène Lupin...
28 years old, hates violence.
The loot is said to be worth
dozens of billions...
Sulak's heists have made him
the biggest public enemy number one.
A very gentle man.
He's never, ever fired a gun.
That's a rule he always follows.
Yes? Boss! Sulak!
So, how about that drink?
Are you free today?
Noon at your café?
But you come alone, right?
You promised.
Of course, I promise.
If you ever find me in the street,
don't worry, I never carry a gun.
- You won't shoot me?
- I never carry a gun.
If we find you, you won't shoot at us?
No.
Then let me tell you something,
if I can't find you, I'll quit.
If you hear that I've quit,
it will be your fault.
- In the news?
- Exactly.
- Okay? See you soon.
- See you soon, pal.
Police! Hands in the air! Don't move.
Take off your helmet.
- Who the hell are you?
- Nobody.
I was asked to deliver this bag
to some guy outside the café.
That's all. I'm a delivery guy.
- Who asked you to deliver that?
- The baker.
Book this little clown.
- Come on.
- I didn't do anything.
Call off the crew. Back to the station.
Hands on the wheel.
Don't do anything stupid,
drive around the square. Come on.
How are you doing?
I'm good. How are you?
- Did you enjoy Cannes?
- Yes, it was ballsy.
You're impressed, aren't you?
You gave me your word,
but you were far from being alone.
You know how the big bosses are.
I can't do what I want.
I told you on the train,
you've got no power.
Look in front of you.
I won.
You lost. I'm out of here.
I quit.
Look, I have more money than Borg.
And I never played tennis.
You'll get bored on vacation.
I'll see you again.
Okay, stop the car, I'm feeling nauseous.
Here.
Give this to Annie
and tell her to call this number
from a payphone.
Everything's inside. Tickets, cash.
No problem.
- Do you have what I wanted?
- Yes.
Here.
Is it the Pole?
He's in jail.
It's another guy, from Marseille.
DRIVING LICENSE
It's terrible work.
And it's not cheap.
But you're famous.
People are scared.
They're asking for a lot of money.
Yes, I know.
I'll call you when I'm in Rio.
Will you join us there?
In Rio? I would absolutely love it.
- Cheers, my friend.
- Cheers.
- Hello?
- My love.
My love, how are you? Where are you?
Too far, I'm too far away from you.
I'm about to cross the Italian border.
We're going somewhere warm, to Brazil.
Brazil?
Yes, you and me.
We're going to spend all this money.
We're gonna go to the beach,
we'll make love, and laugh.
We'll eat good food, bask in the sun,
have a lot of babies.
We need to stop hiding.
We'll stay stuck together forever.
ID check.
- I like that idea.
- Really?
Yes.
- Will you join me?
- Yes.
- Are we leaving?
- See you tomorrow, my love.
- See you tomorrow.
- Hello.
- Buongiorno.
Customs check.
Turn off the engine, please.
Do you have your ID?
Thank you.
Please step out of the vehicle
and follow me.
FRENCH CUSTOMS
I don't understand,
why a Belgian passport?
Why? The passport is Belgian
because my father is Belgian
and my mother is Italian.
It's simple.
- The dad's Belgian, the mom's...
- I get that.
But I don't like your passport.
So I'm waiting to hear back
from the embassy.
They will tell you the same thing,
Are you drunk?
I've wasted too much time.
I have to go to Italy,
I'm expected in Sicily.
I don't understand anything!
Please lower your voice.
Okay?
There's a woman somewhere else
waiting for me.
- What is he saying?
- It's about a woman.
And I didn't tell my wife.
Love.
Yes, it's adultery.
He's going to see a woman in Italy.
This gentleman is married, is that it?
But that doesn't explain the passport.
I don't like it.
But there's nothing to understand.
I've wasted too much time.
Chatting here in this room.
Please. I can't wait any longer,
I have to go to Italy.
This woman is waiting for me. I can't...
Oh, Bruno.
Looking good.
Being blond suits you.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Let's go.
It's over, let's go back to Paris.
By train?
Can I open the window?
Sure.
Therefore, in the name
of the French people,
the court sentences you
to nine years in prison.
Which you will serve
in the Fleury-Mérogis Penitentiary.
The session is adjourned.
Let's go get Bruno.
I'll wait for him at 6:00 a.m.
at the heliport.
Yes, it's my only chance!
Come on, don't wait.
You have to be drunk always.
That's everything.
That's the only question.
For you not to feel the horrible
burden of time, breaking your shoulders,
and bending you down to earth,
you must be drunk without respite.
But drunk on what?
Wine, poetry,
Or virtue. At your leisure.
And if, sometimes, on the steps of a
palace, on the green grass of a ditch,
in the dreary solitude of your room,
you wake up,
with your drunkenness
diminished, disappeared,
ask the wind, the wave,
the star, the bird, the clock,
all that laughs, all that moans and all
that flees, all that sings, speaks,
ask what time it is, and the wind,
the wave, the bird, the clock
will answer you:
"'It's time to get drunk.'"
So as not to be time's martyred slaves,
get drunk, get drunk without respite".
- My love.
"On wine, poetry, love,"
"or virtue, at your leisure."
I'm not even there to hold you in my arms.
Here.
- You're hungry.
- Jail food...
I can't even go to the cafeteria.
- Why?
- Beats me.
They must be scared
I'd hide a saw in coffee grounds.
I heard about Steve.
He was executed.
They didn't give him a chance.
Abolition of the death penalty my ass.
Do you agree with that?
You and your little colleagues?
It wasn't my team.
I handed in my resignation.
- You're not a cop anymore?
- No.
- Because of that?
- Amongst other things.
Since you're in jail,
I don't feel like chasing anyone else.
If you think that I'll stay locked up...
Admit it, you'll miss me.
What are you gonna do now?
I'm taking some time
to travel, read, write.
To write detective novels,
that's a retired cop thing.
Sure, why not?
Keep your head down.
Do your time.
You're still young,
you still have a lot to experience.
Why are you telling me this?
They won't go easy on you
if you go too far.
You've given me an idea.
Maybe I'll write a book too.
- About what?
- Freedom.
Love, the Mediterranean, life.
That's all I'll say or you'll steal it.
Visit's over. Let's go, Sulak.
I don't even know your first name.
Georges.
It's Georges.
- Bye, Georges.
- Bye, Bruno.
Take care of yourself.
Oh, you know me.
Okay, let's go.
- Sorry, it's not easy here.
- Get up.
Come on.
Will you come back?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Ciao.
We'll follow the plan.
I trust you.
The walkie-talkie and the open door.
I'm taking a lot of risks for Sulak.
Wait for my last call
and my final instructions. Later.
Everything's ready, Bruno.
Follow the plan to the letter.
If there's a problem, get back
to your cell. Good luck.
I'm in the main corridor.
Okay, Bruno.
- It's locked.
- It should be open.
It's closed, what do I do?
I don't understand. I left instructions.
I arranged it all.
Bruno? I can't hear you.
If it's not going to plan,
go back to your cell.
- What do you want?
- Americano, two sugars.
- Two sugars.
- Yes.
Bruno?
Get out.
Get out of there.
What are you doing with this?
My love,
once again, I escaped in my dream
to fall asleep near your warm body.
A peaceful feeling.
Heavy body, light mind.
I fly, I float.
I can't feel gravity in the night
that surrounds me with your smell.
I'm not there anymore.
I'm disappearing and finally...
Finally, I find you forever.
Finally.
It has to end one day.
Anyway, I would not have made
a very honorable old man.
But you know, it is my destiny.
I know that.
Sometimes,
I think that this very last escape
will make me
a free man, forever.
FREEDOM