A long time ago, in an era where
there was no concept of 'shinobi',
in an attempt to end an era of violence,
a certain someone ate a forbidden fruit
and gained the power of chakra.
However, as time passed, they
became obsessed with that power.
To bring justice to the world,
what is it that we need?
Power or love?
This question would start an arduous war...
which has continued throughout the generations.
Hey, if you're a Hyuga show us your Byakugan!
If you can't don't show your face around here!
Your eyes are really creepy.
I bet you're actually a monster, right?
You Byakugan monster!
Hey, stop it!
What's your problem?
I'm Uzumaki Naruto!
I'm the future hokage!
The 'future hokage'?
Are you some kind of moron?
Prepare yourself! Kagebunshin no jutsu!
I'm going to beat you!
Me too!
Take that!
We really taught this guy a lesson!
What's up with this "future hokage"?
For being so cocky, let's take care of his red scarf!
It's not over yet! This time I will
bet on an awesome jutsu!
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
Your scarf.  Those boys they--
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Wait...
Thank you so much.
See you!
If the world were to end tomorrow,
who would you like to spend your last day with?
Like that would ever happen.
Just suppose...
The moon began to fall.
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
If the moon started falling, I would protect you.
Like I would ever want you  to protect me.
Write down who you'd want to
spend your last day on Earth with.
That's impossible...
I don't have a Dad or a Mom
or any friends.
Hey, Naruto!
Don't throw away your paper!
But there's no way the world is gonna end!
I'm not saying it will, I'm just saying if  it does!
Well, it ain't gonna happen.
This is a celestial decree
upon the Hyuga clan.
I will ask you one last time.
Let me hear your answer, Hyuga Hiashi.
The answer, which will decide
the future of your clan.
This is the Hyuga's...
...reply!
How foolish.
Today I'm your special
coach, so pay attention!
Naruto-senpai!
I never expected him to become
such high stakes material.
You say 'steak'?
'High stakes' as in popular with girls.
His efforts in the war two years ago
turned him into the village hero after all.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
All right, eat your fill.
Thanks for the food!
Naruto-niichan!
Oh, Konohamaru?
I have something to show you.
What is it?
It's grandfather Hiruzen's stuff.
I found it all during spring cleaning.
Hey, is this...?
Don't you dare call it junk.
They're very precious.
These are...?
They're not junk okay?!
I'm Uzumaki Naruto!
RINNE FESTIVAL
Time sure flies...
sales for the Festival Rinne
have already started.
Naruto-senpai!
Please accept my Rinne Festival present.
For me?
I'm always cheering for you!
I made it myself!
Please accept it!
T-thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hinata!
Oh, Sakura-san.
Knitting something?
That's a surprise.
I'm making a scarf.
W-what is it?
Give it your all, okay?
It's a present for him, right?
He's become really popular lately.
Oh, really?
People even come all the way from other villages
just to take pictures of him.
Oh...
Don't just say 'Oh'.
Hurry up and finish that scarf.
O-okay.
Come on,
you should have more confidence.
Be bold!
O-okay.
It looks quite big, doesn't it?
All done!
I put my heart and soul into it.
I'm sure my feelings will reach Naruto-kun.
But will they?
It's already late.
Maybe tomorrow would be better?
No! I'll give it to him tonight.
Or maybe tomorrow...
No, tonight.
Why don't you just hurry up and
tell him how you feel already?
Hanabi!
If you were there all along why didn't you say so?!
Watching a girl agonize over love is more fun.
That's no way for a child to talk.
I'm not a child,
my Byakugan's perception is
as good as any grown up!
Anyway, look!
Isn't it cute?
Treating your kunai like a toy again.
He'll burst out laughing if your tummy
growls while you're confessing your love.
Who said I was going to confess anything?!
Rather than giving him a scarf,
maybe you should try dressing
a bit more fashionably?
Are you saying that the moon is falling?
The moon is clearly getting closer to Earth.
Is that why there have been
more meteorites lately?
I'll explain...
As the two celestial bodies get closer to each other,
their gravitational pull on each other increases.
Once they come within a certain distance,
The moon's surface will begin to break apart.
I believe a part of the moon's
surface has begun to fall to Earth.
And what will happen?
The moon will completely disintegrate,
and its fragments will rain over the Earth's surface.
If nothing is done, mankind will surely...
Be wiped out, right?
Is this a natural phenomenon?
Or is this a man-made assault?
That is a good question.
It's getting to to that time of year
when ramen really hits the spot.
You only ever eat ramen all year long.
You really like ramen, don't you?
Yup, I love it.
Five more orders of gyoza.
Coming up!
Five orders?!
I can't eat five more orders.
Then don't have any.
Time to eat.
Oh... Can't get this dirty.
Hey, that scarf--
Oh, Hinata.
Join us if you haven't eaten.
It's on me tonight!
He said something made him
happy and he wants to celebrate.
B-but...
Don't be shy, come and sit here.
Join us, Hinata.
O-okay.
Naruto-senpai!
Hey, it's you guys.
Thanks for the presents the other day.
Order whatever you want,
it's my treat as thanks for the presents.
Thank you so much!
Hinata, you can order whatever you want too.
Over here, Senpai!
Let's eat together!
Hinata...?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. Actually, I'm quite full.
Hinata!
Walk her home.
Walk Hinata home?
Why?
Well...
You can't let a young girl walk home alone at night.
Order ready!
Coming!
Hinata's really strong,
no one in the village would dare mess with her.
Hinata!
Oh, you're such an idiot!
Why are you calling me an idiot?
Senpai, the gyoza are ready.
Let's eat!
He can be so dense.
You were going to give him the scarf weren't you?
Yeah.
You can do it, Hinata. Be confident!
Thanks.
But how come you're encouraging me so much?
Well...
Let's both do our best!
Both of us?
Who's there?
Hanabi-chan?
Super Beast Scroll!
Naruto-kun...
I've always gazed at you from afar.
But from now on, I want to always,
always stand by your side.
So I knitted this with all my heart...
Please, accept my feelings.
All right, one more time.
Naruto-kun...
Hinata!
Good evening.
We saw each other earlier at Ichiraku.
Oh, that's right!
What's the matter?
Th-that's a nice scarf.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, it sounds like you're hungry.
If you don't mind instant ramen,
I have some in my room.
Good night!
Didn't you want to talk to me?
Hey, Hinata!
I wonder who gave it to him?
I'm happy for you, Naruto-kun.
Why are you crying?
You're getting the scarf wet.
I don't need it anymore.
Then, I'll take it.
Who are you?
I'm Toneri. I've come to retrieve you.
'Retrieve' me?
Hinata!
What are you...? Let me go!
Hey, you, what are you doing to Hinata?
Tajuu Kagebunshin no jutsu!
Hinata!
Rasen Shuriken!
Hey you... Give Hinata back!
Hold it!
Hinata, are you okay?
Yeah!
Rasengan!
My body is going numb.
My strength...
Hinata!
Your scarf is ruined.
Yes...
Where did those Shinobi come from?
I don't know.
The final day is approaching.
Before that...
You bastard.
Before that day, I will come for you.
Hinata.
What is that?
W-what's going on?
The Earth...
will be destroyed soon.
Your mission is to
rescue Hyuga Hanabi who has been kidnapped.
You'll be working as a four
man team led by Shikamaru.
I'm also granting Hinata's request
to be included in this team.
Thank you very much.
Shikamaru, put your hand out.
Why?
What is this?
A top secret device that only the Five Kage possess.
What kind of device is it?
It's counting down the time until Earth's destruction.
I don't get it.
Why is this necessary for Hanabi's rescue?
Toneri, the one who kidnapped Hanabi,
could be the one manipulating the moon.
What are you basing this on?
My intuition.
It was around here
that I lost sight of Hanabi-chan's kidnapper.
Let's split up and search for clues.
Naruto, take care of Hinata.
Leave it to me!
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
It's Hanabi's kunai.
You brought the scarf?
Why aren't you using it? Aren't you cold?
I-I'm fine.
Anyway, we'd better hurry up and let
Shikamaru-kun and the others know.
Oh yeah, you're right.
What do you see, Hinata?
There's a spring that's glowing
at the bottom of the cave.
A spring that's glowing?
That Shinobi letter is 'A' as in 'Aun'.
It could mean 'This is the beginning'.
Hinata, what can you see
at the bottom of the spring?
My vision is distorted.
Your Byakugan is distorting?
We'll just have to go down and see.
I can't get this wet.
You're being so particular.
What's the big deal if your scarf gets wet?
It's a big deal. This means a lot to me.
There's no need to worry.
I touched the water and didn't get wet.
If the world were to end tomorrow,
who would you like to
spend your last day with?
Like that would ever happen.
Just suppose...
The moon began to fall.
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
Look, the moon.
The match up for the round seven...
Uzumaki Naruto vs.
Inuzuka Kiba.
This is the chunin exam.
Naruto!
Don't you dare lose to a guy like him!
Ninja Art Beast Mimicry: All-Fours jutsu.
Wait a minute!
Here I come.
Stop it, Kiba.
Naruto-kun is fighting Pain right now.
Naruto-kun is fighting alone.
Banshō Ten'in.
Naruto...
What is it?
It's ointment.
Why are you giving this to me?
Just accept it, Naruto.
Thanks, you're a nice person Hinata.
Banshō Ten'in.
Soon I will take you with me.
Why'd you come out here?!
You're no match for him.
This time,
I'm going to save you, Naruto-kun.
I was always crying, and
giving up before even trying.
I made so many wrong turns.
But Naruto-kun, you helped me find
my way and take the correct path..
I always chased after you,
I wanted to catch up to you,
I wanted to walk beside you all the time.
I want to be at your side, always.
You changed me, Naruto-kun.
Your smile is what saved me.
That's why I'm not afraid to die,
if it means I can protect you!
That's because I love you, Naruto-kun.
Hinata...
If the world were to end tomorrow,
who would you like to
spend your last day with?
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
It's Iruka-sensei again, huh?
Write down who you'd want to
spend your last day on Earth with.
Hey, Naruto!
Don't throw away your paper!
But there's no way the world's gonna end.
I'm not saying it will,
I'm just saying if  it does!
Well, it ain't gonna happen.
Uzumaki Naruto.
Me?
Naruto-kun...
What is it?
It's ointment.
Why are you giving this to me?
So dense.
He can be so dense.
You were going to give him
the scarf, weren't you?
Yeah.
You can do it, Hinata.
Be confident!
Thanks.
Naruto-kun, I-
You really love Ramen, don't you?
Yup, I love it.
Naruto-kun, I-
Like, really love it.
Yup, like that time Hinata said she loved me.
He's so dense.
Maybe he doesn't know what love is?
What do you mean?
Like, knowing the difference between loving sweets like
Shiratama dumplings or fruit gelatin and romantic love.
They aren't the same?
Hinata! Oh, you're such an idiot...
Why'd you call me an idiot?
Senpai, the gyoza are ready.
Let's eat.
Hinata!
Senpai.
Uzumaki Naruto.
Hinata...
That's why I'm not afraid to die,
if it means I can protect you.
Because,
I love you, Naruto-kun.
Hinata...
Naruto!
Wake up!
This is a dream!
Oh, Sakura-chan.
You're finally awake.
Is this a trap set by the enemy?
Yeah, it traps intruders in a genjutsu,
and locks them away in a world of memories.
It's a prison of caged memories.
Thankfully Sakura who's
resistant to genjutsu was with us.
Thanks, Sakura.
I was having a fun dream of my brother.
I appreciate you ripping me away from it.
That doesn't sound like gratitude.
Another spring?
Your Byakugan doesn't
work here either, right?
No, my sight is distorted.
All right. As we proceed
be prepared to fight.
Roger.
What's the matter?
About those genjutsu dreams earlier...
What is it?
No, never mind.
Hinata...
I said I'd come for you.
But I never thought you come to me.
Where is Hanabi?
Don't worry, she's fast asleep in my castle.
Return Hanabi!
That will all depend on your answer...
Byakugan Princess.
'Byakugan Princess'?
Hinata...
I...
...want you to marry me.
Marry you...?
It's like a bubble factory.
I get it.
This is where the gatekeeper
who made the bubbles lives.
Gatekeeper?
Naruto and Hinata are taking their time...
We should go back to check--
A crab!?!
That's the gatekeeper.
Hinata!
Naruto-kun!
Get away from Hinata!
You again? You're in my way.
Move.
Where is Hanabi?
Spread out!
Don't destroy the bubbles,
or we'll get caught in that genjutsu again!
Super Beast Scroll!
Fujin, Raijin!
Perfect!
Shadow Stitching!
Sakura!
Damn it!
You're a puppet aren't you?
This is not my body.
Hinata...
Next time, the real me will come for you.
Give me an answer then.
Shut the hell up!
Your fists won't ever touch me.
Not even close.
Did you do this with a single punch, Sakura-chan?
Of couse.
Naruto, if you leave Hinata behind
and expose her to danger again,
you'll get a taste of my fists too.
I know.
Hinata, I'll never let--
I'll not let you out of my sight again.
What is that?
You're already looking away!
I'm not looking away!
What is this place?
Is that island floting?
No.
The surface of the oceans is warped.
There's sunlight underground too.
Isn't that artificial?
A man-made sun?
Yeah.
Hinata, any sign of the enemy?
No, we're fine.
The enemy is aware of us.
Why aren't they attacking?
Yeah, that bothers me too.
It's too quiet.
Leave them be.
Don't do anything until I go to get her.
The eyes are twitching again!
Exquisite...
This Byakugan is very pure.
Hinata?
That scarf... It was really for me?
I see a town about twenty kilometers ahead.
All right, let's go.
It seems like it's deserted.
This town was built a few centuries ago.
Let's split up and search.
So it was a Shinobi village.
A fire?
What is this?
Was there a war here long ago?
What's wrong, Hinata?
There's a spider web.
You can see so much with your Byakugan,
yet you walk straight into a spider web.
You're a silly one, huh?
Naruto-kun...
What is it?
Where is your scarf?
It was pretty warm underground, so I took it off.
I-I see.
I feel a bit cold myself.
Well of course you are,
dressed in clothing like that.
It's just that this is my mission gear!
If you can take it,
I can handle a little cold like this.
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
What?
It's nothing.
What is it?
I said it's nothing!
Come on, tell me.
That was good.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm gonna take a leak.
Naruto-kun?!
A spider web.
You okay?
Yeah.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
I think I hurt my back.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah.
You gave me some ointment back
during the Chunin exams, right?
You remembered that after all this time?
Actually, I only just remembered it.
Thanks.
We have to hurry and rescue Hanabi.
Naruto-kun, I'd like to talk
to you about something...
What is it?
About what was said when
that Toneri puppet appeared.
Toneri?
Here they are!
Hinata, we need you to check something.
What does it say?
It's some ancient writings.
'An ancient oath
crossing the path of humanity.
Like all else,
the Fist of the Tensei eye, the reborn moon,
will destroy man'.
What does that mean?
Maybe this 'Tensei eye'
is making the moon move?
Maybe Hanabi's abduction
is connected to the moon,
Just like Kakashi-sensei said.
Well, his hunches are always spot on...
Unfortunately.
Byakugan Princess!
What is that?
Is this a cemetery?
What is this?
Someone's here!
Byakugan... I sense the Byakugan.
Oh, I'm certain of it!
Oh, Byakugan Princess.
Stay away from Hinata!
Hinata!
What did you do to Hinata?!
The Tenseigan has been revived.
It must be stopped.
Otsutsuki's...
Hinata, are you all right?
Y-yes.
That man said something like 'Otsutsuki'...
That's the original surname
of the Sage of Six Paths.
Otsutsuki Hagoromo...
That was the name of Sage of the Six Paths
before he entered the priesthood.
He called Hinata 'Byakugan Princess'.
Seems Toneri's abduction
of Hanabi is connected.
Knitting again...
Is she going to keep knitting forever?
I guess it takes a lot of time.
Hinata, what was it that you
wanted to talk about earlier?
You mentioned something about
what Toneri's puppet said?
Oh, that. It was nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
I'm sorry, I'd like to be alone.
I see.
Let's check out that village.
Seems like Hanabi's not here either.
We should head back and rejoin the others.
Yeah.
Hinata.
My little sister is in so much danger,
and here I am knitting.
I'm a terrible big sister, aren't I?
That's not true,
you came all this way to
save your sister, didn't you?
If only I'd stayed home that night--
I swear I'll rescue Hanabi!
You don't need to worry.
Thank you.
You're so kind, Naruto-kun.
Well, I'm not being kind just because
I'm in love with you or anything.
I'm just worried about Hanabi.
What was that?
What did you just say?
I'm worried about Hanabi.
Before that...
Before that...?
Hinata...
I...
I love you.
Hinata?
Toneri, are you another puppet?
Where is Hanabi?
Silence.
I came to hear Hinata's answer.
Answer? Hinata has nothing to say to you.
So where is Hanabi?
Hinata.
Hey!
Hinata what's going on?
Naruto-kun...
goodbye.
Hinata!
Give Hinata back!
'Give her back'?
Hinata came to me willingly.
This has been destined since ancient times.
Hinata and I shall be wed.
Wed?
Hinata...
That's a lie, right?
My chakra is...
What are you doing?!
I didn't want to get into a petty fight
and risk getting you hurt.
Hinata...
Hurry up and move forward!
I can't go any further!
Hey, stay in the line!
Don't panic!
The Air-raid shelters were constructed
to accommodate every
citizen in the Land of Fire.
Keep calm. Please keep calm.
Water Style: Water Dragon jutsu.
Lava style: Lava Monster jutsu.
Particle Style: Atomic Dismantling jutsu.
Damn it, my back!
So this place is the moon?
Yeah.
That place we encountered the
crab bubbles may be a conduit.
A passageway connecting
the Earth to the moon.
How is Naruto doing?
It's bad.
He's been almost completely drained of chakra.
Hinata...
So you finally get it, you blockhead.
So beautiful...
Hinata, I want to know more about you.
Why this guy...?
This place is...
Toneri's castle?
Hanabi!
Her eyes have been removed.
Hinata...
I...
...want you to marry me.
Marry you...?
What are you saying?!
Let Hanabi--
Your sister is in my castle.
Hanabi!
I've taken her Byakugan for my own.
You're terrible.
I'm sorry.
It's all part of Hamura's celestial decree.
Hamura?
The founder of the Shinobi of
the Moon, Otsutsuki Hamura.
Perhaps you will understand if I said he was
the younger brother of The Sage of the Six Paths.
Founder of the Shinobi of Earth.
Your Hyuga clan are inheritors
of Hamura's bloodline.
The story goes back many eons.
Several millennia, in fact.
The Sage of the Six Paths,
the elder brother, had some misgivings.
He feared that the Ten Tails,
with its massive chakra
and immeasurable power,
would bring calamity to the world.
So The Sage of the Six Paths
extracted the Ten Tail's chakra
and divided it among nine tailed
beasts in order to weaken its power.
The husk of the Ten Tails
whose chakra was extracted,
namely the Gedo Statue,
was hidden and sealed away on the moon.
In order to prevent the
Ten Tails from being revived,
Hamura decided to live on the moon
and guard the Gedo Statue.
The Sage of the Six Paths however,
became the founder of the Shinobi on Earth.
But Hamura was skeptical of the world that his
older brother was creating.
He decided that if the world created by his
brother went astray from the path of Shinobi,
He would entrust his descendants
with ensuring its destruction.
Throughout the millennia that have passed,
fighting between the Shinobi
on Earth has not ceased.
They continue to use chakra as a weapon,
and ultimately, even
the Gedo Statue was stolen
and the Ten Tails was revived.
Our clan then reached the conclusion
that the Shinobi of Earth only serve
to destroy the world's peace and order.
The world that The Sage of the Six Paths
created was deemed a failure.
So in accordance with the celestial decree of Hamura,
I will destroy the world made
by The Sage of the Six Paths.
When this pure Byakugan
synergizes with my chakra,
it will transform into the Tenseigan.
With its visual prowess I will
gather up the ashes of the Earth
and create a completely new world.
I don't believe your story,
and I'm going to rescue Hanabi!
Despite having no notion of
where this castle is located?
I'll return for your answer.
Hinata!
Good morning.
I'm happy that you accepted my feelings, Hinata.
Hinata-sama, welcome to the castle.
Welcome.
There are only puppets in this castle, then?
They're marionettes left here by our ancestors.
Since my father died when I was young,
I have lived alone in the castle.
We will hold the marriage ceremony here.
Then we will enter the Room of Rebirth
and fall into a deep slumber
until the Earth stabilizes after its destruction.
That's impossible.
The moon will also be destroyed!
Don't worry. This castle is
protected by an immense chakra.
An immense chakra?
Yes, strong enough to move the moon.
What do you mean?
It's the power of Otsutsuki's treasure,
honed from the suffering of my clan.
Where would such a thing be?
That is...
something I cannot reveal.
May I return to my room? It's cold outside.
That's because it's dusk here all year.
Oh, that's right.
Will you knit me a scarf?
A scarf just for me.
Do you refuse?
I understand.
Really? Thank you.
You've made me happy, Hinata.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
It's proof that the Byakugan
is maturing into the Tenseigan.
It will subside with a little rest.
It doesn't seem to be here.
Byakugan Princess.
Activate the Tenseigan!
We are descendants of Hamura.
We belong to the main
family of the Otsutsuki clan.
We were annihilated by the branch family,
who have twisted the interpretation
of Hamura's celestial decree.
Toneri, a descendant of the branch family
is attempting to make the moon
fall into the Earth by using
the power of the Tenseigan.
Only you can destroy the
Tenseigan, Byakugan Princess.
You are...
Otsutsuki Hamura.
Byakugan Princess.
Do not let the world my elder
brother created come to an end.
Hanabi, you poor thing.
I'll definitely find and destroy the Tenseigan.
I can't believe that,
Toneri has been hiding in the artificial sun.
Why wasn't Hinata's Byakugan able to discover it?
Maybe he has a jutsu on the artificial
moon that deflects the Byakugan too?
Where's the entrance?
Why don't we ask them?
What are you doing?
You've alerted the enemy!
Follow me.
What are you doing?
I'll explain later!
So that's how it is.
Sai, retreat.
Super Beast Scroll!
I never imagined this guy's
debut would come after the war
with the world being at peace.
Below is the Chakra Diffusion Cannon.
We'll blast all the meteorites above the equator.
On top is the Chakra Transportation Cannon.
It can transport any target into another dimension.
With these, we'll destroy the moon.
Everyone, get the cannons ready immediately!
Meals are nice when you
have someone to talk to.
Now tell me all about yourself.
It's not too late to negotiate
with the Shinobi on Earth.
What?
You're right...
The Shinobi on Earth have used chakra
and continued fighting.
But it's different now.
In order to protect this hard-won peace
Shinobi have joined together.
So...
They will start another war.
The Sage of the Six Paths'
world must be destroyed.
But...
Never bring that subject up again!
Now be quiet and eat.
That island...
So it's appeared already.
That is the Temple of Hamura.
Once a year, during the Rebirth Festival,
it passes close to the castle.
There's no doubt about it.
The Tenseigan is hidden on that island.
Naruto-kun...
goodbye.
Hinata...
Hinata!
So you're finally awake?
Finally?
It's been three days.
Did something happen between you and Hinata?
No, not really.
You kept groaning her name. Hinata, Hinata.
As well as some other embarrassing things.
But I got to listen in on your mushy side.
It was great research material for me.
Hey...
Naruto.
Let's go rescue Hinata and Hanabi.
Is it hard to face the woman who rejected you?
So Naruto is strong as a Shinobi
but can't handle a broken heart?
Now I know your weakness.
Hey!
Hamura must be happy that you
personally want to pay homage.
The Tenseigan is inside here.
This is...
The Tenseigan.
Then this is Otsutsuki's treasure
that is moving the moon?
Hinata-sama, only those of exalted status
are allowed to see the real Tenseigan.
This is a temple where those
of lower rank come to pray.
I see.
I shall show you the real
Tenseigan after we are married.
My field of vision distorts at only that spot.
So that's it. I've got it!
How long are you going to be like this?
Well you gave up on a woman,
so why not give up on becoming Hokage too?
Yeah, just it give up.
Give up on the woman and
give up on becoming Hokage.
What was that, Shikamaru?
Are you trying to pick a fight?
I don't care what happens
between you and Hinata.
But you're a Shinobi!
Come with me.
I'm going to my room to rest.
I'm looking forward to the finished scarf.
I feel it, I can feel it.
The beating in my eyes!
It will be born very soon.
The complete Tenseigan.
Sakura-chan...
This is the result of infusing nearly
every ounce of her chakra into you
trying to keep you alive.
Sakura-chan!
Naruto.
Sakura-chan, I'm so sorry.
Are you going to depend on Sakura to heal
not only his body, but his heart as well?
Can you do it?
You have a point.
I see.
I never imagined you'd confess your love first.
Remember long ago, when
you said you loved me?
But wasn't that because I loved Sasuke-kun?
You didn't want to lose to him.
But it's the real thing this time, isn't it?
Hinata is a great person.
She's almost too good for you.
But it's over.
Hinata went to Toneri.
You're so stupid.
It's obvious she had a reason
that she couldn't reveal.
When a girl truly falls in love,
her feelings don't change that easily.
They can't change.
I understand how she feels very well.
This is...
Tenseigan.
I'll stop the moon!
What's the meaning of this?
You're wrong!
What?
Hamura's soul entrusted me
with the true celestial decree.
You have distorted Hamura's teachings.
Hamura never wished for
the destruction of Earth...
the Sage of Six Path's world!
You've betrayed me.
Please hear me out! Hamura is...
Silence! They're lies.
I don't believe it.
There is only one celestial
decree that Hamura made,
and that is to end the world,
of the Sage of Six Paths!
Damn it!
So you were knitting this
for him and not for me?
I'm going to make it so
you'll never betray me
ever again!
Hinata...
This big idiot finally understands,
the meaning of the scarf you
gave me when you went to Toneri.
Now, I know from the scarf
you painstakingly knitted,
and took so long to finish,
that your love can't be unraveled so easily.
Naruto-kun...
Wait for me.
You've loved someone like me all this time.
Now, as a man, there's something
I've got to say to you.
Hinata, I swear I'll save you!
Raikage-sama, the Chakra Cannons are ready.
All right. Men, load the chakra.
Yes sir.
First, we'll fire the Chakra Diffusion
Cannon to pulverize the meteorites.
Pulverize. Powderize!
Cover me!
Right!
Rasen Shuriken!
Shadow Paralysis jutsu!
Next...
We're storming the castle!
Right!
Sakura-chan!
Thanks, Naruto.
No need to thank me.
I owe a debt to you that
I'll never be able to repay.
What a pain.
Why are you hiding it?
It's irritating, and it's
clouding my judgement.
Naruto, can you sense Hanabi's chakra?
Hanabi is in that tower over there.
Sakura, Sai... Take care of Hanabi.
Roger!
Hinata!
You bastard!
Your fists won't ever touch me.
Naruto, where's Hinata?
In there!
I'll handle things here.
Thanks.
Move!
I won't let you pass.
All right, the puppet show begins now.
Hanabi is above here.
What?
This way!
Hinata...
Wind Style: Sky Sand Defensive Wall.
At six o'clock! It's a huge one!
Everyone! Crane wing formation!
Roger!
The Sixth Gate Of Joy!
Damn it!
You're...!
If he's not around,
The only one who can protect the village
is me.
Sasuke.
The meteorites are gone.
Hokage-sama.
What is it?
Hiashi-san?
Chakra capacity at 75%
76, 77...
One after the other.
Now, go in.
Hinata!
What did you do?
Give Hinata back!
Fine, I'll give her back.
Stop, Hinata!
What do you think of my wife's skills?
Damn it!
He's controlling her.
Hinata...
Bear with it for just a moment.
Hinata isn't a doll for you to manipulate!
Hinata belongs to me. I'm taking her back.
Hinata...
Get back.
It's too early for you to wake up.
Damn, the final pulsation!
Naruto-kun!
Hinata!
Naruto-kun, I'm so sorry...
I...
I understand, you don't need to say anything.
I'm the one who has to apologize.
But what about him?
Now's our chance,
we have to destroy the Tenseigan!
Tenseigan?
Hanabi!
How terrible.
She's just a child.
Hinata...
If we destroy this the moon
should stop its approach.
Got it. I'll use my Rasengan.
No!
There is a cursed jutsu cast upon this eye.
Only someone of Hamura's
bloodline can touch it.
Anyone else will be completely
drained of their chakra.
What?
Eight Trigrams: Twin Lion Shot
I can't destroy it!
Hinata, infuse me with your chakra.
Then together we might be able to break it apart.
Okay.
Let's go.
These are...
The Tenseigan was made out
of clusters of Byakugan?
What?
Hokage-sama,
the moon has stopped its approach.
What?
Chakra capacity at 95%
96, 97, 98, 99...
Chakra is at 100%
Chakra Diffusion Cannon fire!
Yeah!
What just happened?
An urgent message from the Cloud Village,
a Five Kage summit is being convened.
All the meteorites have been destroyed.
So you had such a weapon
like that hidden away?
It seems we can not be too
careful with you, Raikage-dono.
Tsuchikage-sama, let's drop the sarcasm!
Next up is the Chakra Transportation Cannon.
We'll blow up the moon!
Blow up the moon?
What's happening?
Shikamaru!
Hinata, are you all right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Save that for later.
Anyway, what happened?
The artificial sun disappeared.
We destroyed the Tenseigan.
It was the power source
driving everything here.
The moon should've stopped moving too.
What?
The treasure that my entire clan
offered up their eyes to realize...
the Otsutsuki treasure...
How dare they!
Hanabi!
Thank you.
This is yours, right?
Isn't that the scarf Toneri ripped off?
How did you know?
When I pulled Toneri's jutsu from your body,
I was able to see your memories.
You were going to give it to Naruto, right?
Did you make it for me?
Y-yeah...
Can I have it?
But, it's in shreds.
I don't care.
I mean, I still want it.
Thank you.
I'll cherish it.
Naruto-kun...
What's the matter?
The clock...
It's moving.
With these eyes, Naruto,
I will destroy your world.
It's too dangerous to destroy the moon.
As long as that bomb we call a moon exists,
the Earth will not be safe!
Now let's discuss this calmly.
Right now, the moon has stopped its approach.
No, it hasn't stopped.
What?
Why is the clock ticking again?
I don't know.
W-what was that?
Kurama!
It's Toneri!
Silver Wheel Rebirth Explosion!
Chakra capacity at 90%
Hokage-sama!
Hiashi-san would like to speak with you.
Hiashi-san?
Do not destroy the moon...
I'm certain that Hanabi and Hinata are there.
What do you mean by that?
Bad news...
What is it?
The Nine Tails is on the moon's surface.
What?
Chakra capacity at 95%
Raikage-sama, an urgent
message from Hokage-sama.
What does he want at a time like this?
Please hold off on the chakra cannons.
Naruto and the others are on the moon.
That can't be helped.
They have to be sacrificed for
the sake of humanity and the Earth.
We're going to fire the
Chakra Transportation Cannon!
Raikage-dono...
What is it?
I'm asking you too.
Can you postpone for one hour?
What?
I have to agree.
Mizukage?!
Naruto is a hero of the last great war.
He's worth betting on.
Tsuchikage?!
Just one hour will do.
For them, that amount of time
will be worth a lifetime
that can never be replaced!
What do you base that on?
My intuition.
Hinata, are you okay?
Y-yes.
No!
I'm taking Hinata back.
You can watch his last moments from there.
Hinata!
Naruto-kun!
The world created by the
Sage of the Six Paths is a failure.
I will put an end to both the Earth and to you!
I'll never let the Earth be destroyed!
Rasen Rengan!
Golden Wheel Rebirth Explosion!
Naruto-kun!
What is that?
The moon...
The moon has split apart!
What?
What's happening?
Hey, Hokage...
There's ten minutes left!
It's finally over.
It's not over yet!
What?!
Chou Oodama Rasen
Tarrengan!
It's useless. Just give up.
Like I'd ever give up.
It takes time to knit a scarf.
The deeper the feelings that you want to convey,
the longer it takes to knit.
With this, it's over!
Like I'd ever let you!
To convey your feelings,
it takes much, much, more time!
That's why...
I can't let it end so easily!
You...
...defeated me, with one punch.
The Tenseigan is fading?!
Hinata!
Naruto-kun!
I'm taking back Hanabi's eyes.
No, stop!
Why you!?
This is over.
Not yet!
Sakura, are you okay?
What about Naruto and the others?
I don't know.
W-what is going on?
I'll end it all with these eyes.
Puppet rebirth!
You're annoying!
Naruto.
Hinata!
Toneri, please stop already!
All you did was follow your
ancestor's misguided teachings.
Quiet! As the last survivor of the Otsutsuki clan
I must fulfill Hamura's celestial decree!
Naruto-kun?
All my chakra's being sucked out.
Now you'll feel the power of Hamura,
the power to move the moon!
Naruto, it's over for you!
Hinata?
What?
This is not the end yet.
Why?
Hamura's chakra flows within me too.
Stop already.
End it, end the world of
The Sage of the Six Paths!
I will destroy the Sage's world
that has fallen into darkness
with the light of justice!
What?
His jutsu absorbed the sun's energy
and now he's passed his chakra limit.
Naruto-kun?!
Don't! It's too dangerous!
Time's up.
Fire the Chakra Transformation Cannon.
What's wrong?
I can't shoot at Naruto.
You must stifle your personal feelings.
The very existence of Earth depends on this.
Move! I'll fire it!
Raikage-sama, there is
something written on the moon...
What?
Kurama is writing something on the moon's surface.
That Shinobi character means...
'Mission accomplished'.
The mission was successful!
I see.
Emergency announcement to the entire world...
The moon has stopped,
thanks to the effort of these five:
Shikamaru, Sakura, Sai, Hinata, and Naruto.
Earth and it's future are safe.
My intuition usually ends on a high note.
Making me write letters...
I'm no good at calligraphy!
Sorry, Kurama.
This is...
Hamura's soul guided me here.
Toneri, everyone on Earth will welcome you.
I will remain on the moon and atone for my sins.
Toneri...
One day... One day, come to Earth.
The moon will never again approach Earth.
Never again.
Naruto, there is something I have to ask you.
What is it?
That scarf...
Who gave it to you?
Oh, this.
My late Mom made it for me.
What?
My grandpa must've kept it for her.
Mom...
I see.
I'm so silly.
Hey, Sis!
How long are you going to chitchat?
I'm going on ahead of you!
Hurry up, the passageway
is starting to disintegrate.
Let's go home to Earth.
Yes.
Hinata...
What is it?
Back in school when we were asked
who we'd want to spend
our last day on Earth with...
I couldn't write anyone's name down.
I didn't know my parents
and didn't have any friends.
But now, I know exactly who I'd choose.
I want to stay with you!
Now and forever, until the day I die.
I want to be with you, Hinata.
Naruto-kun...
Hinata, put your arms around me.
O-okay.
Don't let go, okay?
I won't.
I'll never let go.
What are you doing?
Sis!
Naruto! You're going to crash into the ceiling!
Like I'm going to let that stop me!
Hinata...
Naruto-kun...
Thank you.
Doushite? Doushite naite umarete
Why? I wonder why we cry when we’re born.
Itsuka nagarete hoshi ni natte ikun darou?
Some day our tears will flow until it reaches the stars.
Boku ra wa doushite? Doushite osowatte nai no ni
Why? I wonder why we know how to shed tears,
namida no nagashi katta wa shitterun darou?
despite not being taught how.
Afureru shizuku wa taema naku
This overflow of teardrops shed incessantly,
sosogareta aijou no akashi de
is the proof of our affection.
Michibikareru mama yuruyaka ni sotto tsutatte kitan da
Gently and softly guides to go and come back.
Kokorokara karada e karada wa kokoro e
From heart to body and from body to heart.
Soranaru ikutsumono karamiatta rasen no moyou
Continuous pattern of many intertwined spirals.
Sono hitotsu hitotsu ni mirai ga mietanara
One by one our future can be seen,
nagameteiru kono sora wa hora uchuu ni mieru
in the sky we’re looking at, look, look to the universe.
Doushite? Doushite tsuki wa itsudemo
Why? I wonder why the moon always,
Nani mo iwanaide yami wo terashiterun darou?
without saying anything, is shining light upon the darkness.
Boku ra wa doushite? Doushite kodou no kazu ni
Why? I wonder if we know that there’s a limit,
kagiri ga aru no wo shittete mudanishichaun darou?
it makes these heart beats completely futile.
Mune ni kakaeteru utsuwa no
The size of the vessel carried in one’s chest,
okisa ni kachi mo miidasun janakute
is not to determine our value.
Sono naka ni aru betsu no okina tane ni inochi wo kanjitai
It's if something else inside exists to experience life.
Donna ni me wo konashite jibun wo miyou toshitemo
No matter how hard you look, if you try to see by yourself.
Boyakette yoku mienai ya sono uchi miushinatte shimau
It's blurry and you will end up completely losing sight of them.
Sagaseba sagasu hodo chirakashite shimau nara
At the end of your searching, if it's completely scattered,
miyoumimare datte kono te de sou tsukureba ii
learn by watching others by doing this, you’ll be fine.
Ikiru tte iu koto sore wa kitto
When talking about living is surely,
sukoshizutsu tebanashite iku koto
little by little parted with many things.
Saigo no hitotsu wo ushinau sumu toki soba ni itte
After parting with the last one, please by my side,
namida wo kureru hito ga iru sore de ureshii
I will give you tears and they will be happy tears.
Kokorokara karada e karada wa kokoro e
From heart to body and from body to heart.
Soranaru ikutsumono uketsuge rasen no moyou
Continuous pattern of many succeeding spirals.
Kurikaesarete koto ga mou iya da to omoeta toki
Doing this repeatedly until the time comes i say no way.
menomae no keshiki subete ga ima uchuu ni natta
now the entire scenery before my eyes is become universe,
uchuu ni natta
it become universe.
Daddy!
Play with us!
Hey, don't go outside with bare feet!
All right, Boruto, Himawari...
How about a snow ball fight?
Snowball fight?!
Take that!
Hey, Boruto!
All right, Mom is joining in too!
Hey, you guys know when Mom
gets serious, she's super strong!