♪♪
Tony Stark: God, it seems like a thousand
years ago...
I fought my way out
of that cave...
Became Iron Man...
Realized I loved you...
I know I said no more surprises, but...
I was really hoping to
pull off one last one.
Peggy Carter: The world has changed.
None of us can go back...
All we can do is our best...
And sometimes the
best that we can do...
is to start over.
♪♪
Thor: I saw all these people die.
Steve Rogers: I keep telling everybody
they should move on...
Some do...
But not us.
Natasha Romanoff: Even if there's a...
Small chance...
We owe this...
To everyone who's
not in this room
to try.
We will.
Steve Rogers: Whatever it takes.
Nebula: Aaaaahhhh!
Clint barton: Whatever it takes.
Natasha Romanoff: Whatever it takes.
Tony Stark: Whatever it takes.
♪♪
I like this one.